export default data = [
  {
      question: "The ending of the movie did not come as a _____ to John because he had already read the novel that the movie was based on.",
      options: ["vision","focus","surprise","conclusion"],
      correct_option: "surprise"
  },
  {
      question: "In order to stay healthy and fit, John exercises _____. He works out twice a week in a gym.",
      options: ["regularly","directly","hardly","gradually"],
      correct_option: "regularly"
  },
  {
      question: "Traveling is a good way for us to _____ different cultures and broaden our horizons.",
      options: ["assume","explore","occupy","inspire"],
      correct_option: "explore"
  },
  {
      question: "The story about Hou-I shooting down nine suns is a well-known Chinese _____, but it may not be a true historical event.",
      options: ["figure","rumor","miracle","legend"],
      correct_option: "legend"
  },
  {
      question: "According to recent research, children under the age of 12 are generally not _____ enough to recognize risk and deal with dangerous situations. ",
      options: ["diligent","mature","familiar","sincere"],
      correct_option: "mature"
  },
  {
      question: "Helen let out a sigh of ______ after hearing that her brother was not injured in the accident.",
      options: ["hesitation","relief","sorrow","triumph"],
      correct_option: "relief"
  },
  {
      question: "Research suggests that people with outgoing personalities tend to be more _____, often expecting that good things will happen.",
      options: ["efficient","practical","changeable","optimistic"],
      correct_option: "optimistic"
  },
  {
      question: "No one could beat Paul at running. He has won the running championship _____ for three years.",
      options: ["rapidly","urgently","continuously","temporarily"],
      correct_option: "continuously"
  },
  {
      question: "If you fly from Taipei to Tokyo, youâ€™ll be taking an international, rather than a _____ flight.",
      options: ["liberal","domestic","connected","universal"],
      correct_option: "domestic"
  },
  {
      question: "Jack is very proud of his fancy new motorcycle. He has been _____ to all his friends about how cool it looks and how fast it runs.",
      options: ["boasting","proposing","gossiping","confessing"],
      correct_option: "boasting"
  },
  {
      question: "The ideas about family have changed _____ in the past twenty years. For example, my grandfather was one of ten children in his family, but I am the only child.",
      options: ["mutually","narrowly","considerably","scarcely"],
      correct_option: "considerably"
  },
  {
      question: "The chairperson of the meeting asked everyone to speak up instead of _____ their opinions among themselves.",
      options: ["reciting","giggling","murmuring","whistling"],
      correct_option: "murmuring"
  },
  {
      question: "Although Mr. Chen is rich, he is a very _____ person and is never willing to spend any money to help those who are in need. ",
      options: ["absolute","precise","economic","stingy"],
      correct_option: "stingy"
  },
  {
      question: "If you want to know what your dreams mean, now there are websites you can visit to help you _____ them.",
      options: ["overcome","interpret","transfer","revise"],
      correct_option: "interpret"
  },
  {
      question: "The memory _____ of the new computer has been increased so that more information can be stored.",
      options: ["capacity","occupation","attachment","machinery"],
      correct_option: "capacity"
  },
]
